If you're a personal trainer,
you should be very excited because your
job fucking
sucks.
You start work earlier than anyone else in
the world.
Then you're to go to work,
then take a break, then go back to work,
then take a
break for a few hours,
then come back to work
when everyone else has left work,
then get home late in the evening,
barely get any sleep,
come back to work again.
Can you imagine if I had a job application
out?
"Hey, I want to pay you okay money.
You're going to start work at 6:00 AM,
have
three lunch breaks,
and get home at 7:00 PM.
Oh, and by the way, your entire workday
is one-to-one meetings, and every
single person expects you to be at their
best." You'd be like, "No, I'm not doing
that." But you love fitness
and the idea of going to work in
activewear, so you
decide to do the job. My name
is James Smith.
I have done thousands of hours of personal
training.
I've built one of the biggest fitness
empires.
I've had hundreds of thousand people using
my coaching app, and also became a
"Sunday Times" number one best-selling
author, and broke a lot of records in the
nonfiction publishing space in fitness.
So you're probably thinking,
"That sounds awful." Well,
let me tell you this.
What a lot of you don't realize as
personal trainers is you probably won't do
this
job forever,
and the lessons you're going to learn from
growing and operating a
fitness business,
you will take with you into the next thing
you do.
But before we get into that,
let me give you some tips
that I wish someone had come
along and told me 10 years ago